Synced & corrected by reggielist
www.addic7ed.com
You see what happens?
You live with your grandmother
for three days,
and your brother becomes a Christian.
[RABBI RECITES
"MOURNER'S KADDISH" IN HEBREW]
Amen.
Where's Judy?
Um...
Judy's not coming.
She's... not gonna be
in our lives anymore.
Isn't she, like, your best friend?
What? No.
No, not at all.
Barely knew her.
Then why did you let her live with us?
You guys wanna have this chitchat later?
Henry's about to become
a child of Christ.
Excuse me, rabbi.
I just wanna say
it was such a nice service.
I love that prayer.
It was beautiful.
What did it mean?
That despite losing someone we love,
we still praise God.
Even though God
took away the person we love?
If we want God to forgive us,
we have to forgive Him.
I like that.
It's nice to think of Abe
up in Heaven with God.
That is nice to think of, but...
there is no Heaven.
- Really?
- No Hell either.
Really?
No matter how much bad someone's done
or how many people you've hurt?
Well, in the Jewish faith,
if you've hurt someone,
you've got to try to make amends.
Find a way to compensate
for what you've done wrong.
Thank you.
Shalom.
Henry Theodore Harding,
we now wash away your original sin.
What's original sin?
Basically, we're all
born guilty and sinful.
But then when we get baptized,
it's like we get a do-over.
Then, all you have to do is ask for
forgiveness and you get a clean slate.
Isn't that nice?
She's totally fucking lying to you.
Through baptism,
we are all one in Jesus Christ.
I baptize you in the name...
- of the Father and the son...
- Sorry.
...and of the Holy Spirit.
Mrs. Harding. Hi.
Judy Hale killed my husband.
Yeah?
Yeah? What do you mean, "yeah"?
I mean, as of recently, I've been
made aware of her possible involvement.
No, no. No, it is not possible.
It is definite.
She confessed it to me.
Okay.
I...
I feel like you're being
cavalier about this.
I'm not trying to be cavalier.
- Well, then go arrest her.
- It doesn't work that way.
There are much bigger factors involved.
What factors? God!
The way you talk
fucking annoys the shit out of me.
I'm sorry. But I can't.
It involves another investigation.
And until that plays itself out,
my hands are tied with Ms. Hale.
And even then, if she confesses,
it's not enough to warrant an arrest.
She is a murderer and she is
walking around free as a fucking bird.
You have to do something.
Okay, I can get you a restraining order.
That'll take me about 24 hours.
She killed my husband
and then she moved in with me.
A restraining order isn't gonna do it.
Thank you for fucking nothing again.
Mrs. Harding, wait. Mrs. Harding.
For now, try and take comfort
knowing that you have your answer.
Isn't that what you wanted?
You want me to take comfort
in the fact that we live in a world
where everyone knows what the truth is
and there are no consequences?
There will be consequences,
I assure you.
Oh, no. I assure you.
Look at us working together again.
Look at us.
You know, I have to say, having Charlie
at my house has been a real godsend.
It's like having Ted back.
Well, yeah. It's just a phase.
Charlie will come home
when he's done being mad at me.
- Well, I'm glad to be able to help.
- Okay.
Be someone you can turn to.
That's what family's for.
You look tired.
Lorna, I just sold two
of these units for you all cash.
What is it gonna take for you
to just lay off?
Well, you didn't sell anything.
What?
Steve Wood pulled his deposit
this morning.
I thought you knew.
- Why?
- I don't know. He's your client.
Oh, shit.
Well, don't dwell. Circulate the trays.
And do one more Swiffer
of the bathrooms.
I want that faux marble spotless.
Yup. Of course.
Hi. Would you like one?
- No.
- Okay. Great.
- May I offer you a pinwheel?
- No.
Hi. Would either of you like
to try one of these?
- No.
- Okay.
Hi.
Good afternoon. Would
you like a pinwheel?
- No.
- Okay. Good.
Hi.
Get the fuck out of here!
- Please don't make a scene.
- Then get the fuck out!
I don't want you to get in trouble.
Let me help you.
No, don't fucking help me.
- Shh.
- You shh!
Okay.
- You look really nice.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
How dare you fucking show up here?
I'm working for Lorna
to keep a roof over my kids' heads,
to keep my life together.
A life that you destroyed.
I know.
That's why I'm turning myself in.
I just wanted you to know I'm gonna
ask for the maximum sentence.
It might be the chair
if that's something that they still do,
but the worst punishment of all
is losing you.
Well, I already turned you in.
Yeah. Okay. That's... You should have.
That's right.
- Yeah. Yeah. That's ight thing to do.
- Good for you.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
It doesn't even fucking matter,
because your confession isn't enough.
So you get to go walk free and fuck
with my head as much as you want to.
I don't wanna fuck with your head.
- Then what do you fucking want, Judy?
- I want to just make amends.
I want you to be okay.
You want me to be okay?
Yeah.
You hit my husband and left him to die.
Then you stalk me, you
move into my home,
you get my children to trust you.
You are a fucking sociopath.
- I love you.
- I fucking hate you.
Okay.
Stay the fuck away from me.
If there's anything that I can do...
You know what you can do? You can
disappear off the fucking planet.
Okay.
I have Ted's gun in... in my purse.
So, if I see you again
or you go anywhere near my family...
I will shoot you in the fucking head.
Do you understand me?
Yeah... I do.
Get the fuck out
and don't even come near me.
Get the fuck out of here, Judy.
Go. Now!
Yes, Howard. I'm not a fucking idiot.
I know...
Obviously somebody
fucking talked to the...
I don't know who.
Listen, I'm handling it. I just
gotta move some cash around at the bank.
Hang on. Would you hang on?
Fuck! I gotta call you back.
Stavros.
Stavros... Hey.
[SPEAKING GREEK]
Yeah, I know you can speak English,
but my Greek is pretty good, right?
Oh.
How much were you looking
to withdraw from the joint account?
All of it, please.
In a cashier's check.
So you wanna close out the account?
That's right.
Well, we're certainly
sorry to see you go.
Uh, may I ask why you decided
to leave Orange Coast Trust?
I'm going away.
Hey, Karen.
Sorry it took me so long
to get this back to you. I just...
Anyway, whatever was
in it was delicious.
It was my take on Mexican lasagna.
Mmm, right. Right.
Well... thank you.
There weren't too many raisins?
Uh-uh.
No way.
- All right. Well, thanks.
- Mm-hm.
Um...
Would you...
Do you wanna... come by later,
like, after the kids go to sleep
and have a glass of wine by the pool?
You mean socialize?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Great.
- So I'll see you there?
- Cool.
- By the pool.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Your pool...
What?
Your house?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
- Do you want me to bring anything?
- No. No.
I could whip something up. I don't work.
No, please don't.
- Just don't do that.
- Okay.
Thanks. See you later.
- See you later.
- Bye.
I'm sorry, that account has been closed.
- Sorry, what?
- Yes.
The joint person on the account?
Ms. Hale.
She was here earlier.
She was here earlier and she what?
She what?
- She...
- She closed the account.
Cool.
Um... Thank you.
Fucking Judy! I'm gonna
fucking kill her!
Snap and kick. Snap. Kick. Good. Okay.
♪ Every breath you take ♪
♪ Every move you make ♪
Henry, yes.
♪ Every bond you break ♪
♪ Every step you take ♪
♪ He'll be watching you ♪
Owen, very good.
Yep. Yep. Yep.
♪ Every single day ♪
♪ Every word you say ♪
♪ Every game you play ♪
♪ Every night you stay ♪
♪ He'll be watching you ♪
Keep going.
♪ Oh, can't you see ♪
Judy, hi.
I'm sorry, this is a closed rehearsal.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry.
I just have a little gift for Henry
in honor of his baptism and I thought...
Well, maybe you could
give it to him for me.
Sure.
I'm his godfather, after all.
He's very lucky to have you.
Yeah.
Hey, what happened with Jen?
Why did you move out?
She didn't tell you?
No, she won't talk about it.
So I assume a violent outburst
is imminent?
Just be kind to her, please.
She really needs a friend right now.
Okay.
I do need you to go.
The kids aren't audience-ready.
♪ I keep trying baby, baby Please ♪
- Alright, hop into bed, honey.
- Okay.
I just have one last thing
I need to go over with you.
- Okay.
- Okay. You see this over here?
This white thing?
- Yeah.
- That's a sensor.
So if the bird that you think is
your daddy comes to the window,
you can't talk to him
until I turn the alarm off.
It's okay.
Judy got me a bird I can keep inside.
- What?
- You wanna see? It's for my baptism.
Um...
When did you see Judy, Henry?
She came to the Holy Harmonies practice
but Christopher kicked her out.
He doesn't like people seeing us
in an unpolished state.
Okay.
If you ever see Judy again,
you tell me, okay?
You tell me immediately.
I... I hope I see her again.
- I miss her.
- I know.
- I know you loved her.
- You love her too.
We can make other friends.
Right?
Good night.
- So glad we're doing this.
- Me too.
Funny, we've been neighbors eight years,
and I've never been over.
Oh! That's... Yeah, that's funny.
It's a lovely backyard.
Oh.
You really went for it
with the security back here.
Yeah. Well, thanks.
You can never be too safe, right?
Right.
Did your ADT package come with the
Remote Arm/Disarm Via Mobile App?
Yeah.
- Why do you know...
- I'm kind of a home safety nerd.
Cool.
Cool-cool, cool-cool.
Where do you keep your gun?
Oh, I... I don't...
Yeah, I'm not, like,
not really a gun person.
- I get it.
- Mm-hm.
I didn't think I was either.
But then Jeff got me this adorable
pistol for Christmas and, honestly,
call me a convert.
Okay.
Fun fact.
Did you know if you ask someone
to leave your home and they don't,
you can totally shoot them?
- No, that can't be true.
- It is.
- Fun.
- Mm-hm!
- Okay.
Do you want any more wine?
I should probably get myself home.
If I drink too much,
I break out in full body hives.
Actually, wait.
Um...
Would you mind showing
me how to use this?
Uh...
I'm assuming you do that.
Armed, stay.
Shit!
What's going on?
It's okay, honey. Just stay in
your room. Just lock the door.
- Lock the door.
- What?
Charlie!
Mom, open the damn door!
Charlie, you scared the shit out of me!
You scared me.
Those lights are fucking aggressive.
Okay. Hold on. Let me
turn this thing off.
Disarmed, ready to arm.
Hey, you're home.
Yeah. Grandma kept calling me Teddy
and touching my face.
Well, that's disturbing.
Yeah.
She has a pill problem.
Mmm.
Hand them over.
- I... I wasn't gonna sell them.
- Mm-hm.
I was saving her from herself.
Really?
Really.
Okay.
I'm glad you're home.
Honey, I'm...
I'm so sorry
that I've been such a shit mom.
- It's all right.
- No.
No, it's not all right.
I'm sorry that I...
that I get so angry sometimes.
And that you saw your dad and me fight,
especially that night.
Okay.
No, really.
I need you to forgive me, Charlie.
I want a clean slate with you.
Just don't be an asshole anymore.
Well, that's, you know,
kind of a big ask.
Come here, baby.
Mmm! Oh, God, I love you.
I love you too.
What?
What are those words I just heard?
You didn't say, "Fuck you too"?
- Yeah.
- You said, "I love you too"?
No.
Best day ever.
- Best day ever.
- Okay.
No. I just need a little more.
Come on, now.
Better put this fucking gun away.
Oh, my God.
Judy?
Where's Judy?
I need to speak to her immediately.
Well, she's not here.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
You know, you could've told me that
you're pulling that offer.
It really did fuck me, you know that?
Yeah, well, Judy fucked me.
- There you go. She ruined my life.
- Well, you're not alone.
I told you. Anywhere Judy goes,
chaos follows.
Yup.
You did.
I was just trying to look out for you.
Do you want a drink or something?
I can get you a glass.
I don't need a glass.
She destroyed me, Jen.
My whole life, my family,
everything I worked for,
it's all gonna disappear.
What happened?
I can't really get into it.
What? She run someone else over?
She told you?
Yeah.
Shit.
Would it make any difference if I...
if I told you I'm sorry?
Not that I was the one driving.
You were in the car?
Jen, that was...
honestly one of the worst moments
of my entire life.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
It...
It just killed me not to tell you,
especially once...
I don't know, once I got to know you.
You know, in so many ways,
I feel like we are...
we are in this together.
- You know?
- Are we?
Yeah.
That's why I need you to help me.
I gotta find Judy.
Can you help me do that?
Why didn't you stop?
What?
That night.
Oh.
I mean, I wanted to.
Judy said she wanted to go back,
but she couldn't.
Why not?
I don't... I don't know.
I don't know. She just didn't.
And you didn't.
- Don't do that.
- Do what?
Don't turn this into some
"blame the man" thing.
That's bullshit. Don't.
We both know what Judy is capable of.
Yeah. And I know what you're capable of.
Oh, you have no fucking idea.
Hey, her hand was on the wheel.
Her foot was on the gas.
So don't fucking look at me like that.
Fuck you.
Fuck you! She was driving. She did it.
- What did you say? Huh?
- Okay.
After she hit him, what did you say?
I don't remember.
Holy shit!
We have to get the fuck out of here.
Drive the car, stupid!
I'm so sorry.
One of the worst moments in your life,
and you don't remember?
I don't remember.
I'm so sorry.
Judy would have stopped.
Did you not hear me the first time
I said it? I don't remember.
Okay. You need to leave my house
right now.
Jesus fuck.
- I'm a good guy, Jen.
- No, you're not a good guy.
You're defending her,
and you're pulling a fucking gun on me?
I want you to leave my house.
Give me the gun Jen. Come on honey.
You don't know what you're doing.
- Don't come any closer!
- I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me where
the fuck Judy is.
What the hell are you doing?
Get out of the road!
Jesus!
Hello?
Judy... I need you to come home.
www.tvsubtitles.net