You're welcome.
Good morning to you. Why am I welcome?
What am I looking at?
That is a piece of the car
that killed Ted.
Hard evidence that I procured.
Now, you can have it
and run it through the scanner.
- What scanner?
- I told her there was no scanner.
Hey. Good to see you again.
Uh-huh. I'll move past the fact
that you brought in your own cop
and ask where that came from?
This is from Shandy Addams,
the girl that found Ted.
And you went to her?
No, she came to me.
Why does that matter?
It matters because there is
a process for these things.
A process?
The process that has given you
no leads or suspects?
You guys have been at this for months
and you have found nothing.
I'm at it for one day, I find this.
Now I wonder what else is out there.
I wanna see everything you have.
All of it.
- I wanna see the whole file.
- No, I can't do that.
Yeah, I know you can do it
because I Googled it.
You're allowed to see it, but there is
a reason that we don't show evidence
- to the loved ones of the deceased.
- I want to see it.
It is disturbing
and it might be hard to handle.
You don't know what I can handle.
Yup.
Good job. Pound it out.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Out of curiosity, are there any
toll roads that branch from the scene?
There's the one in PCH
and the ones that lead to Yorba Linda.
CCTV from those?
Lots, but without a license
or a make of the vehicle, we...
You know, in Santa Ana,
we had a case like this.
Uh... Mrs. Harding?
What?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Synced & corrected by reggielist
www.addic7ed.com
Wood, Wood &amp; Wood.
How can I help you?
[SPEAKING IN GREEK]
Girl, you can't just go in there.
- Girl!
- Where is it?
- Judy.
- Steve.
Hi.
Sorry to interrupt.
Uh...
Yeah.
Bye, guys. God, it's a great suit.
I love your pocket square.
All right. Bye. Thank you.
- Why are you here?
- She's got a piece of the car!
- What are you talking about? Where?
- Jen, she has a piece of our car.
She's putting it through...
- the scanner right now.
- Easy.
Which will lead to us and then
she's gonna find out that it was me,
so I need to know where the car is!
- Right now!
- Hey. Hey.
Will you calm down, okay?
I'm taking care of it.
- Okay.
- The car is not gonna be a problem.
Why? Where is it?
It's someplace safe.
Is it at your mother's?
- It's at my mother's.
- Oh, great.
Womderful. I can't wait to get
wrapped up in all this with Eileen.
She's at the lake house.
You don't have to worry.
She's been going through
a lot lately, so lay off.
- With what? Her leather allergy?
- Yes, actually.
That's not a real thing.
Oh, that's not a thing. But somehow
you're ruled by the moon?
- Go back to your Greeks.
- Judy. Where are you going?
- Don't go to my mom's house.
- I'm going.
Judy!
Bye, girl.
Hi! It's Judy. Leave me a message.
Thanks.
Judy, hi. Um...
It's me. Uh...
Sorry. I just, um...
I really need to talk to you.
I think you're the only person
who would understand. I'm...
I'm at the station and...
I saw...
I saw pictures of Ted after the accident
and I thought I could
handle it and I'm...
I don't think I'm handling it now.
Please, can you just call me back?
I guess I just... I need you.
It's gross.
Sorry. Um...
Okay. Bye.
Wow.
Told you the car
wasn't gonna be a problem.
This is not what I expected.
Yeah, well, I'm sitting there thinking,
"How do I get rid of this thing?"
You know. It's always
gonna be somewhere.
What if it's everywhere?
Right? You dismantle it, you break
it down to the component parts,
you dump them
in three different junkyards in Mexico,
and, poof, the car is gone.
- No car, no crime.
- Exactly.
No matter what they find out,
they don't have evidence,
or an eyewitness tying us to the scene,
they have nothing.
Ted was the only witness.
Yeah. And Ted's dead. So we are good.
- Where did you even learn to do this?
- Online. Watched a few videos.
I pick up things up pretty quick, girl,
you know that.
It turns out certain things come apart
a lot easier than you'd expect.
Yeah.
- Happy birthday, baby.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
God, it's Jen. She keeps calling me.
Pick it up. Tell her I said hi.
- No.
- Why?
What if she knows? What if they already
put the piece through the scanner?
What if they already
The scanner doesn't scare me.
I'm sorry. Would you calm down?
First of all, my dad is buddies
with the sheriff, okay? They golf.
And, B, I grew up with
those Laguna cops.
They are beach town cops. The only thing
they're gonna catch is a wave.
They have technology.
Gee, if they can trace these parts
to a junkyard in Rosarito
with one little piece of a car,
then hats off to them.
- I will turn myself in.
- Stop it.
I'm taking care of it, okay?
I'm seeing everything from the outside
and I'm ten moves ahead, I promise you.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Okay. Thank you.
But we really need to do it today.
We don't know how fast
things will start moving.
I got meetings back-to-back all day.
My morning's already ruined.
Fine! Go to your meetings
and I'll just finish everything.
Just show me how to use the tools.
I'll keep going.
- Really, Ponyboy?
- Yes.
I can't think of this
as half-finished anymore.
I just really, really need this
nightmare to be over.
Okay.
I will cancel my meetings
and we'll take care of this today.
Thank you.
There you go.
I'm seeing someone.
That's great. I'm super happy for you.
Oh! Look at this wainscoting.
- It's wonderful.
- Mmm.
I'm in a cottage and I am loving life.
Mmm. Honey, you could do
your scrapbooking in that corner.
Oh, love!
And the light
in this area too. It's just to die for.
- Right, Jen?
- Yup.
I mean, in the morning, the sun just
drapes across this floor and you feel,
I don't know, forgiven.
Ooh, this kitchen! Beautiful.
I'm not crazy about
those sliding glass doors.
I hear you. But a look at that deck!
I mean, let me show you
where the grill goes.
Now, let's talk modern cabinetry.
I used to be into a more rustic look,
you know, farm style this and that,
the barn door, the porcelain knobs.
But, lo and behold,
now, and if you knew me,
you would not see this coming...
Now I like sleek. I like simple.
So that's why I'm gravitating
to these more modern fixtures.
This is a bamboo fusion, isn't it?
I don't know, actually.
Wouldn't you say? I think it's a bamboo
fusion or is it anutmeg finish?
A nutmeg finish or a bamboo fusion?
I saw this on a magazine.
It definitely said, "Bamboo fusion."
I even clipped it out
and saved it for a moment like this.
I'm always losing things,
aren't I, honey?
Ha, don't get me started.
I even got a filing system and I spilled
Earl Grey all over it and tea stains.
- It does.
- I know.
- Isn't that sad?
- Oh, it's so sad.
- No, this is not sad.
- Oh, honey, are you okay?
- No. Please excuse me for a second.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God! Do I fucking look okay,
you vapid fucking twat?
- That crazy massage?
- That was Sedona.
It wasn't Sedona. It was Santa Fe.
Maybe you went to Sedona
with your new boyfriend.
No. You and I... went to Sedona.
Remember?
Remember that room with the fireplace
and fountain and you were all,
"I don't care about vortexes,"
and you became the Vortex Guy.
Okay. I...
I let you talk about it
for, like, two seconds.
- That doesn't make me the Vortex Guy.
- Oh, yeah.
I liked the hike we went on, though.
Even though I burned my dick.
Oh, my God.
I almost forgot about that.
Yeah. That's a "hashtag
never forget" for me.
Well, that's what you get for
not wearing any underwear
with floppy shorts
and falling asleep in the sun.
You made me not wear underwear
for sperm count, remember?
There's something else
I want to ask about that trip.
What?
Do you remember when we went to
the Petrified Forest?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay. Do you remember the sign that
said if you take any of these rocks,
you're gonna have bad luck
for the rest of your life?
Yeah, I kind of remember that.
Okay. Well, I never told you,
but I heard a radio show about that.
About how these people
who had taken rocks
sent them back years later with letters
saying that, "My life has fallen apart,"
or, "My wife left me,"
or, "I lost my job."
And they all attribute it
to stealing a rock from that place.
Did you steal one of those rocks?
Oh, come on! That's such bullshit.
Really?
It's just people blaming
their crappy lives on something else.
Perspective, Judy. It's important.
- Perspective and mindset.
- Okay. Fine.
But did you take one?
I mean, I remember wanting to.
But, no, I didn't take one.
- You promise?
- Yeah.
Here's that healer's info.
She does a thing
where you hold a baby chick.
You just hold a chick. It will help.
Thank you so much.
I'm really sorry again.
Okay.
Before you say anything,
I need you to know...
This isn't working.
It wasn't... it wasn't that bad.
It was very that bad.
Let's just say an atmosphere of polish
and professionalism was not achieved.
Okay. You know what?
I promise you it will
never happen again.
It won't. Because I can't anymore.
You can't what?
This. All of this.
What is this? What are you pointing at?
Jesus, help me find my strength.
We can't pretend this is the first time
you've shit the bed on a sale, honey.
You keep driving clients away.
You scare people. You scare me.
So what is happening here right now?
Are you breaking up with me?
Just professionally.
And I didn't want to,
but you've made it impossible.
Okay. Hm...
I know that I haven't been at the top
of my game the last few months,
but I don't know if you've heard,
my husband was murdered.
So, yeah, I haven't
really been in the best place.
Look, I pray for you
and your boys every day.
I have tried to be a good friend to you.
But it's not like your issues
started the day Ted died.
I've been thinking about having
this conversation with you for years.
Ever since the Shorewood condos,
when you ripped apart that ficus.
Oh, my God. You were with me on that.
We both hated that ficus.
It did not belong there.
What about Crystal Cove, when you yelled
at that sweet couple, the Walshes?
What? It wasn't...
She was racist.
She was 80.
Jen, your anger is untenable.
And I don't know how
to help you with it.
I just know I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
Hi. Excuse me. Do you know
where I could find Judy Hale?
Never heard of her.
Okay.
Are you a friend of Judy's?
Yeah.
Hi.
I'm Jen.
Oh, you're the nice lady
that she stays with?
And you must be Abe.
My whole life.
- Sit down.
- Thank you.
Uh, Judy, uh...
- called in sick.
- Really?
I don't think she's sick.
Well, she's probably
with that asshole, Steve.
Hmm.
I think you might be right.
You okay, sweetheart?
Yeah. I...
just had a really shitty day.
Actually, a few shitty years.
Oh. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
'Cause I think maybe I deserve it.
I wouldn't be too sure of that.
I don't believe in deserves.
You think the child at Auschwitz
got what he deserved?
Oh, God. Of course not.
No, I just...
I just think I deserve this day.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Thanks, Abe.
I can see why Judy loves you so much.
Me too.
Look at us.
Sharing a little Cuervo Tradicional.
Oh, is it tradicional?
That's how you're supposed to say it.
You don't have to roll the R
a bit or anything?
Man, I can't wait to
get rid of that thing.
I wish I'd never bought you that.
You didn't know.
The truth is, I wish I'd done
a lot of things differently...
with us.
Yeah. Me too.
We were good together.
- Mmm.
- I know we had some hard times, but...
yeah, there were some great times too.
And I really hope that...
this new guy...
knows how to take care of you.
- Don't do that.
- Do what?
The whole "I hope this new guy
can take care of you the way I did."
And that thing that you're doing
right now with your eyes.
What? I can't use my eyes?
The way that you're
looking at me, just stop.
I'm looking at you like a person.
I do not think you look
at your grandmother like that.
You have no idea how I look
at my grandmother. My grandmother...
was a very handsome woman.
She was.
- What?
- It's that.
- That thing.
- Don't know what you're talking about.
- It's not a thing.
- It is a thing.
There's no thing. You're making it
a thing by calling it a thing.
I am definitely not making it a thing.
It is already a thing that exists
and I'm pointing it out. And you
don't need a microscope to see it.
- Oh, so I'm in science class now?
- Oh, yeah.
You are.
- Shut up.
- What?
I know you know what you're doing.
How about we do a little test?
- I'm gonna close my eyes.
- Okay.
- When I open them...
- Mm-hm.
You tell me if there's a thing.
- Are you ready?
- Fine. Sure.
Judy?
Oh.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Uh... Thought I'd stop by,
see if you're doing okay.
And I came across this piece of pie.
That's very sweet of you.
Come on in.
Can I get you a glass of wine
or a beer or something?
- Beer. Beer would be great.
- Beer it is. All right.
- There you go.
- Thanks. Yeah.
How you holding up? I know this
morning was a lot to take in.
Yeah.
How was the rest of your day?
Incredibly shitty.
Worst one yet.
Of course not as bad
as the day my husband
went for a run and never came back.
Because that was a...
that was a real bummer.
Right.
Anyway, that's very nice of you
to check up on me.
I'm sure none of the reason
you're here is to see Judy.
Oh! Nope. God, no.
No, I'm really...
- I'm trying to avoid her, you know.
- Right. Right.
- By showing up to where she lives?
- Yeah.
Exactly. And ponder what kind
of baked goods she might like.
Mmm. It's carrot cake, by the way.
- Carrot cake.
- And, uh... she's not here.
- He went out for a run?
- Hmm?
Ted. You said
he went for a run that night?
Yeah.
I saw in the file he was wearing Vans.
Yeah. Yeah, he was wearing Vans.
He didn't like running shoes.
Didn't even own any.
Something about toughening up
the bottom of his feet.
Yeah.
This IPA is good.
It's, like, hoppy. It's really hoppy.
Oh, you know what?
I'm so sorry, I really...
I should take myself to bed. I'm just...
- A big day tomorrow.
- Oh. Yeah. Okay. Okay.
Figuring out my life.
- Yeah, got it.
- I'll tell Judy you stopped by,
- not to see her.
- Mm-hm.
- Not to see her.
- No. Of course not.
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Bye, Nick.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
Okay.
I really did love that car.
I know you did.
- All right.
- Careful.
Oh! Uh...
I gotta be honest with you. Um...
I...
I did.
You did what?
Uh...
Take one of the rocks
from the Petrified Forest.
Didn't you?
- No.
- Come on.
No, I did not, Steve.
Why not?
What do you mean, why not?
Because those are sacred rocks.
Because they asked you not to take them.
Because there is a sign there that says,
"This is bad luck."
Oh, please. My life is ruined
because I stole a rock?
But not because I'm a jack-off?
Come on. I promise you,
it doesn't matter.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Okay?
I'll call you later.
Hey.
- What the fuck?
- Hi.
Look, I don't even know what to say.
- Jen...
- No. It is so fucked up.
Jen, I'm so sorry.
You were with Steve, weren't you?
I... I was.
You know what? You could at least
have texted me back. Jesus, Judy.
The last time someone that I loved
didn't call me back, he was dead.
Oh, my God.
You're right.
- I'm so sorry. I'm such an asshole.
- I needed you today.
Like, really needed you.
And that's very hard for me to admit.
I'm sorry.
I mean, how did it go
with the police this morning?
I don't wanna fucking talk about it.
I'm going to bed.
Okay?
Steve?
Seriously?
What does that guy have over you, Judy?
- I wish I could say.
- Hmm.
Good night.
Okay. Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Bye.
It's a new day, Judy.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
They found the make and model
of the car that killed Ted.
- What?
- Uh-huh!
And that was Nick and he's gonna get me
a list of every registered owner
of that kind of car in Orange County.
- Oh, wow!
- I know. Oh, my God.
It's a 1966 Mustang. Isn't that weird?
It's just so weird to know that now.
- It's creepy, right?
- Kinda.
But it's, like, yeah, this happened.
This happened
and this is the person that did it
and this is the car that they drove.
- It's... it's amazing, right?
- God.
- It's super amazing.
- Yeah.
I mean but...
- here's where my mind goes right now.
- What?
If you were the person that hit them,
wouldn't you maybe have
gotten rid of the car?
I mean, wouldn't that be, like,
the first thing you would do?
Maybe.
But... maybe not.
If you really think about it,
that would look really suspicious.
- Don't you think?
- No.
I mean, if it was me,
I wouldn't get rid of the car
because of how guilty
it would make me look.
It's kind of, like, the worst thing
you could possibly do.
Like putting a fucking bulls-eye
on your head.
But, yeah, it doesn't matter.
Even if the person got rid of the car,
we'll still know they had it.
- Right.
- Mm-hm.
All right. I'm gonna shower.
It's a new day, Judy.
www.tvsubtitles.net