["SING, SING, SING" PLAYING]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- [CHEERING]
Synced & corrected by reggielist
www.addic7ed.com
Judy Hale.
That's the artist.
Sorry. I'm new here,
so I still need the thingy.
[CHUCKLES] So how much
would a Judy Hale set me back?
Well, between nine and twenty thousand,
depending on the size.
Nine and...
- Jesus!
- Ooh!
Looks like these are all sold.
I guess she's famous or something.
Yeah, I've heard of her.
Hey, so what can you tell me about the
'66 Mustang that's usually
parked out front?
Oh, I don't know.
Um, actually, let me go ask my boss.
Cool. Thank you.
[SIGHS]
[STEVE SPEAKING GREEK]
- Hey there.
- Hey.
- Hey, Steve Wood.
- Steve?
- Yeah. And you are?
- I'm dying to know if your Mustang's
for sale.
- Sorry. What did you say your name was?
- I didn't.
Hey you know,
I drive by this gallery all the time.
- It doesn't seem like you're ever open.
- Yeah, gallery hours.
- It's a thing. It's a real thing.
- Hmm.
Right. So, the Mustang. Where is it?
Sorry. I'm not gonna be able to help you
with that one, broseph. Uh...
- Maybe it belongs to one of my artists.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Probably definitely.
Probably definitely Judy Hale?
Uh...
No. I mean, I don't know. I'm not sure.
Why don't you call me if you get sure?
All right. Will do...
Detective.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Judy, your breakfast is ready.
I made it myself.
Oh! Look at you. That is so sweet.
Yeah. It's pancakes.
They're vegan... mostly.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
[JEN CHUCKLES]
I wouldn't eat that.
- No.
- Seriously?
- It's the thought.
- It is the thought.
How was your dance class?
Oh! It was amazing.
I'm sore as shit right now,
but thank you for making me do that.
How are you doing?
- I'm doing a little better.
- Okay.
No, you're not.
- No, I'm not. I'm sorry.
- Oh, honey, honey.
[JUDY SOBS]
It's just hard.
I'm trying to process the idea
that I'm never gonna have children.
- You know, you can always adopt.
- [SCOFFS]
Yeah, I'm 41 and homeless,
send me all your children.
I wouldn't... open with that.
All I ever wanted was to have a family.
You... you have us.
You're a part of this family.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Oh, gosh.
That was supposed
to make you feel better.
It does.
Uh Mom, I need a new laptop.
Mine's getting old.
Not now, Charlie.
Judy's having a moment.
What, so my needs come last?
Do you know how much a new laptop costs?
I can't even swing
the mortgage this month.
So your laptop is a
little low on my list.
- Oh, boy.
- [JUDY] Wait, what?
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
It's just money's a little tight.
- It's very tight.
- Let me contribute.
No.
Can you pay a mortgage
with a debit card?
I still have the one
that I shared with Steve.
- You do?
- Yeah.
He has so much money. I never touch it
myself, but he wouldn't miss it.
No, no. You know, I don't need
Steve Wood paying for my mortgage.
Oh does Steve wanna buy me a new laptop?
You know, if you want a
new laptop, go get a job!
Did Henry need to get a job
to pay for his stupid fucking choir?
Yeah. You wanna join the fucking
church choir, sure,
I'll pay to see that.
I'd rather get hit by a car.
- You watch your mouth!
- Too late.
Don't you dare disrespect
your father like that ever again!
Me disrespect him?
You are one to fucking talk!
Go to your room!
I'm gonna call Grandma,
because at least she gives a shit.
You know what? You can't
go running to Lorna
every time you need something Charlie!
Lorna, no one sells like me.
You know that.
I would be a huge asset to this team.
So, you need me.
As much as it pains me
to admit that, yes, I do.
My income has been... really stalled.
Because your business
partner dumped you.
- Don't.
- Because you're a real estate pariah.
Oh, Jesus Christ, Lorna!
Isn't it exhausting hating me this much?
- I don't hate you.
- Thank you.
- I'm just consistently disappointed.
- There it is.
You may pretend not to remember,
Jennifer, but I do.
One day, you were my protege
and then you deserted me,
tempted by whatever fruits
Christopher dangled in your face.
No, I don't think
that's an apt metaphor in this...
Do you have any idea
how it feels to be abandoned?
Yes, I do.
But this job isn't for me, Lorna.
It's for the boys.
They are craving
stability and electronics.
Just please... help
me give that to them.
Well played.
You know they're all I have left.
And I let them down.
What are you talking about?
The night Ted died,
he called me.
Yeah, you've, um...
you've mentioned that.
[FAINT HEARTBEAT]
I can't stop thinking about it.
I didn't answer.
[HEARTBEAT FADING]
He didn't leave a message,
but I know he needed me.
A mother knows.
And... I wasn't there.
Where were you?
I may have...
taken a powerful sleeping aid.
Okay. Look, Lorna,
don't beat yourself up about that.
It's not your fault that Ted died.
- Isn't it?
- No.
If a butterfly flaps its wings in Japan,
doesn't it cause a hurricane in Florida?
I honestly don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, I've lost the thread,
but I'm the butterfly.
Okay.
All right.
What's this over here?
Is this a new listing you're working on?
Yes. That's Sapphire Terrace.
I have exclusive pre-sale rights.
Six units, ocean-facing.
Perfect for a rich bachelor.
Mmm. Really?
Know any?
Yeah.
I think I might.
I've just been working here for
three years and I still get the minimum.
You know, when we hired you,
you were like,
"Pay me what you want, Angela.
I just wanna help, Angela."
Just give her a raise.
Abe, I got this, thank you.
It's just that I live
with my family now,
and I would really like
to be able to pitch in.
Just give her what she wants,
or I'll go ape-shit.
- Abe!
- What?
I'll talk to management.
Thank you, Angela.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Hey.
- Judy, I need to talk to you.
There's nothing to talk about,
'cause I'm not pregnant, so don't worry.
Hm-mm, it's not that.
A detective came by the gallery today,
started asking me questions
about the Mustang.
- Freaked me out.
- What kind of detective?
I don't know. A black one.
Oh! That's the guy I was dating.
That's Nick. We're fine.
How are we fine?
Why were you dating a black detective?
Don't be racist.
- It's not racist to call him black.
- It is when you say it.
You know what, he's
actually really sweet.
He's trying to help Jen find
the hit-and-run driver.
- You're the fucking driver!
- I know!
But I was getting them
off our scent, okay?
And it was the only thing
that was making Jen happy.
Jesus Christ, Judy.
Why don't you just fucking confess?
- You clearly wanna get caught!
- No, I don't.
She can't find out. I can't lose her
and I can't lose those kids.
- I'm gonna fix it.
- You're gonna fix it?
- Yes.
- 'Cause you're a mastermind?
Yes. I'm gonna call Nick.
And say what?
He asked if you own the Mustang.
- He did?
- Yes!
He's on to us
'cause you fucking led him there.
I told you to listen to me
and you couldn't,
could you, fucking bleeding heart.
God damn it.
You have no idea how to work people.
I'm sorry
I'm not as good a criminal as you!
- Hey. Hey!
- Ow!
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
You listen to me. Let me get
one thing straight here, okay?
If anybody goes down for this,
it is you. You were driving.
You are the criminal.
I'm the only eyewitness.
- But you said we were in this together.
- Well, now it's every man for himself.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
And look, it's your friend calling me.
- Why is Jen calling you?
- Jen, what's going on?
You killed that nice lady's husband,
didn't you?
It's okay.
But don't let that asshole
push you around.
I don't know what to do.
What do you wanna do?
I wanna tell the truth.
Well...
they say the truth shall set you free.
I'm telling you, Judy
Hale and Steve Wood
are responsible
for the Harding hit-and-run.
Okay. But do you have any evidence
that isn't entirely circumstantial?
His gallery, TKG Arts, is the
registered owner of a '66 Mustang.
And whose art does he sell? Judy Hale's.
Okay, Mr. Prager, that's interesting,
but I can't arrest
people on coincidence.
They were engaged. They were in cahoots.
Cahoots is not
a chargeable offense either.
They broke up a few
weeks after the crime.
Guess what could ruin a relationship?
Fucking killing a guy could.
- Right.
- Then she moves in with Jen Harding?
The widow?
They did it. I know it in my bones.
[SIGHS]
Mr. Prager, you were romantically
involved with Ms. Hale, correct?
- I was, but...
- I'm assuming that didn't work out.
No.
And you were a detective
for the Santa Ana PD, is that right?
- Yes.
- And yet
you haven't reported to work
in three months. Why is that?
Because I took a...
You know, none of this is relevant,
by the way.
- I took a leave of absence.
- Was it voluntary?
- [SCOFFS] Who cares?
- What was the nature of the leave?
Psychiatric.
Thank you.
Now, I appreciate the tip,
but I have work to do.
Well, thanks for meeting me here.
- Yup. Nice place.
- Yeah.
You know, Jen, when you called,
I got to be honest,
I got a little nervous.
Nervous, huh? Do I make you nervous?
No, no, no. It's just that everything
that went down with Judy,
and I'm not sure what she told you,
but, you know, I was surprised.
Mm-hm.
- Girl code. I know it's a thing.
- Not really.
I don't wanna talk about Judy right now.
I wanna talk about you.
- Okay.
- And I wanna talk about
what I wanna do for you.
Well, I mean, for us, really.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[EXHALES]
Wow, Jen, this is, um...
I gotta admit, this is...
I have... I have thought about this.
[CHUCKLES]
You've thought about what?
You know, I've thought about...
No. What?
You know.
- Wait. What were you talking about?
- What are you talking about?
I'm... I'm talking about
selling you a home.
Sapphire Terrace.
Oh. Oh!
What, did you think
I was coming on to you?
No, no, no, no, no.
- 'Cause, like, I would never...
- No.
- Ever.
- Right. Obviously.
Yeah. Well, it doesn't
seem very obvious.
- No, it was.
- 'Cause, I mean, I'm not after you.
Steve, I am after your commission.
Yeah! Honest woman. I love it.
Tell me about the place.
Okay. So, every unit is customizable
and, well, there's this. So...
- [STEVE] Pretty hot.
- Fuck, yeah, it is.
The units are selling really fast.
So I would put an offer in today.
Easy, tiger.
You must really need that commission.
I just know a great opportunity
when I see one.
But, yeah, I do. I do need it.
- How big you say it was again?
- Twenty-four hundred square feet.
I mean...
But, hey, you know what?
If you knock down that wall
to the adjoining unit,
you'd get a 48-hundred-square-foot
palace in the sky.
Room for a family.
Yeah.
I'll take them both. All cash.
- All cash?
- Mm-hm.
So... $8.6 million in cash.
Uh... yeah.
Is that enough commission for you?
Yeah.
Good.
Welcome to your new life.
Welcome to yours.
Holy shit.
Oh, shit. Fuckin' A. Fuckin' A. Hell.
Wow. Everyone's coming to
talk to me today. Hmm!
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Hello, Detective. You look well.
Your hair is different.
- No, it's not.
- Oh, okay.
I have something to tell you.
Something that... Do you have any water?
- No.
- Okay, 'cause I'm a little bit nervous.
I have something I've wanted to tell you
for a long time, but I didn't know how.
- I'm listening.
- Yeah.
Maybe like a soda or anything to drink?
- My mouth is, like, so dry.
- Ms. Hale.
Have you ever harbored a secret?
It's crippling.
And I think it's taking a toll
on my health,
and is probably the reason
why my womb is prematurely aging.
Do you have, like, a lozenge
in there or anything in your desk?
- I don't.
- Okay.
- Judy.
- Yeah?
[HEARTBEAT]
[JUDY BREATHING SHAKILY]
Steve Wood is a money launderer.
Uh... What? [STUTTERS]
- Come again?
- He's a money launderer.
A big one.
- He's a money launderer?
- Yeah.
And a tax evader.
He has a shell company.
It's called TKG Arts.
It's a gallery, and frankly
some of the stuff is pretty good.
But mostly he uses it to funnel money
for his international clients. Greeks.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I mean, that's a pretty big accusation.
I assuming you have
evidence to support this?
This is where he keeps his paper trail.
That's what it's called, right?
Paper trail?
You have my full cooperation.
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello, everybody.
Mommy's got presents.
Mommy should probably stop calling
herself Mommy, but Mommy like it.
Hello.
Oh.
Hey, Lorna. So you got my message.
He bought two.
All cash.
Paperwork's being prepped.
He's wiring the deposit tomorrow.
So, you're welcome.
That's not what... Charlie called me.
Okay. If this is about the laptop,
Mommy took care of it.
Jennifer, I want you to know
this is not my doing.
What's not your doing?
Oh...
I'm moving out.
I'm gonna live with Grandma.
- What?
- He wants to live with me.
I heard him.
Char, I know we had a little fight
this morning but, come on, a laptop.
It's not just about the laptop.
Look, Charlie, I know that things
have been hard since your dad died,
but I promise you,
they are gonna get so much better.
- I can't live with you anymore.
- Why?
- What did I do?
- You know what you did...
the night Dad died.
Good. Fucking go!
I never wanna see your
fucking face again!
We had a fight.
Charlie, people do that in marriages.
He didn't wanna live with you anymore.
And neither do I.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Sorry.
Did you say all cash?
- [JEN] Hey.
- [GASPS] Hey.
Jeez, you scared the shit out of me!
What are you doing
sitting there in the dark?
Do you want me to get that Cabernet?
Or... something stronger?
Where are the boys?
They asleep?
They're at Lorna's.
Everything okay?
What's going on?
It's my fault.
What's your fault?
That he's gone.
Wait. Do you mean Charlie or Henry?
- Ted.
- Ted?
What are you talking about?
The night that he died...
we had a fight.
Um, well, okay. People fight.
That doesn't make it your fault.
No. No, I...
I was really angry.
What were you fighting about?
It's too hard to talk about it.
You can tell me.
Come on. You can tell me anything.
He hadn't...
He hadn't touched me in over a year.
Okay. Well, he was having an affair.
So that is on him.
No.
No. He... he stopped after...
after my, um...
mastectomy.
Oh.
I just thought it wouldn't matter.
That he... he...
he could get past...
all of that. But he couldn't.
- I'm so sorry.
- And he didn't want me anymore.
But I needed him.
He...
He made...
He made me feel so disgusting.
And I... [SNIFFS]
was just so resentful.
And...
that night, it just got heated and...
and I hit him.
The last thing I did before
he walked out that door was...
was hit him.
Okay.
I punched him in the face.
Well, I'm sure he said something
that made you...
Oh, God. Judy, please stop.
Stop trying to make me feel better
all the time.
I'm just saying.
I'm sure there was a good...
No! It is my fault that he's dead.
He wasn't even here.
- He was out on a run, Jen.
- Oh, God. He wasn't running.
It was one o'clock in the morning.
He was on that road
because he didn't wanna spend
another second in this house with me.
I killed him.
Oh, God. I keep trying to find...
[SNIFFS]
the person to blame and...
I drove him away.
I hit him.
I fucking hit him.
[JEN SIGHS]
No. I hit him.
What?
- I hit him.
- Okay.
What are you talk...
I hit him.
No. I hit him.
- No. I hit him.
- I hit him.
- I hit him. Judy. Oh, God.
- He was walking out the door and...
- I had a '66 Mustang.
It was so dark,
and I was driving,
and I didn't see a bend
in the road,
and I took it too fast, and I...
He was just right there.
I wasn't even sure what had happened.
And then I wanted to go back...
but I couldn't.
[JUDY SNIFFS]
And I thought if I could just...
somehow make it up to you,
if I could...
help you somehow,
or if I could be your friend...
Please forgive me, Jen.
Please.
I had no idea that I was gonna
love you so much,
or the boys, or that you guys
would become my family.
Please...
say something.
Please tell me what I can do
to make it better
and to make things right,
and I'll do it. I would do anything.
Please tell me what I can do.
[JUDY SOBS]
You can die.
[JUDY] No. No.
Abe, you up?
[ANGELA SIGHS]
I'm so sorry, Judy.
He went peacefully.
No.
No!
I didn't get to say goodbye.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
["SING, SING, SING" PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
www.tvsubtitles.net