You want to confess something?
Wait, how do you even know where I live?
I dropped Judy off here one night
when she was... was...
Didn't, um...
- This is about something else.
- Okay.
Oh. Oh, God. Oh, God.
What's happening here? Um...
You... you okay?
I'm sorry. This isn't professional.
No, no, it's fine, you're fine.
It's... it's, uh...
Hmm. Why you crying?
- I don't want to get into it.
- Okay.
- Michelle left.
- Oh.
- She moved out.
- Oh. Wow. I'm so sorry.
Bad timing on my part.
I mean, yeah, okay,
I guess I maybe was just holding out hope
that we would get back together.
Oh, yeah.
But no, she just thinks that I lost myself
in my job,
that I always see the worst in people.
Oh, I'm sure that's not the case.
Do you think I want to be a cop
all the time?
You think I like being the person
people are afraid of?
"Oh, let's not invite her to game night.
She'll arrest us all for smoking pot."
That's not even illegal anymore.
Okay, well, it's a bad example,
but it's really hard to "turn it off" when
you're dealing with criminals all day.
Right.
I'm sorry.
No, it's... it's okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Take your time.
Yeah. Yeah, sorry.
Okay.
What did you want to say?
- I killed Steve Wood.
- Oh, Jesus Joseph Christ.
"I don't know where to begin.
I just know this has to end.
I know you think you're the reason
all our problems started,
but they existed long before we met,
and I'm so glad that we met.
You are the best friend I've ever known,
the best person I've ever known.
You're a better mother to Charlie
and Henry than I could ever be.
I know that they may not be
the kids you dreamed of,
but I'm hoping you'll find it
in your enormous heart
to take care of them
and be their legal guardian.
I'm so sorry I lied to you.
I'm sorry I betrayed you.
I'm sorry I couldn't
forgive you sooner for Ted.
But no matter what you think,
you've paid the price.
Now I need to do the same."
This seems right.
How much farther?
Um, I think we're close.
Okay. All right. It's this way.
Morning.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
Beautiful day, huh?
- Yeah.
- It's great.
Come on, Daisy.
- Have a good one.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Walk me through this again.
- Okay.
- Mr. Wood showed up at your house, angry.
- Yeah. Very.
And I asked him to leave, and he wouldn't.
You know, my kids were upstairs.
I was worried that he would...
Anyway, he said some things
that really upset me,
and I don't know, but something
inside me just took over,
and the next thing I know,
he was...
If I was married to you, I'd want
to kill myself too you miserable cunt.
What did you do?
Dead?
Yeah.
Why'd he show up at your house
in the first place?
He was looking for Judy.
Hey, good morning.
Hi!
Oh, nice, you made pancakes?
Sure did! With some chocolate chip action,
your favorite.
Aww, thank you.
Is Mom coming down?
Um, she's not here.
Where is she?
She probably went for a run.
Yeah, she probably did.
Who's hungry?
Oh, I am.
There you go. Well, you better dig in.
Get all up in there
while they're still hot.
Aren't you gonna have some?
Yeah.
Cool.
I'll be right back.
Judy, hey!
Hey, hey, Karen!
- Getting an a.m. jog in?
- I sure am.
- Me too!
- Yeah.
Not sure if you heard,
- but Jeff and I are separating.
- Yeah, I did, I'm sorry about that.
Yeah, working on my revenge bod
before I hit the dating apps.
Forget that, you look great.
- Oh, thanks.
- Sure.
Hey, if you ever want a run buddy,
we can get a little Google Cal...
Okay, no worries.
You got your own flow going.
I totally respect that.
It was fun catching up!
Wait, slow down.
You're telling me you dragged his body
through these woods with no help?
Yeah, yeah, 'cause I was a dancer.
- Very strong core.
- Yeah, right.
Okay, look.
I know you have a photo of Charlie
driving Steve's car.
Okay, but he got the car from my storage.
He is a teenager
with an underdeveloped frontal lobe,
and he saw something he wanted,
and he took it.
He's an idiot.
But he is not a killer.
All right, you know what?
Yeah, this is looking very familiar to me.
That's because we've just circled back
to where we were.
Wait, wait. We did? Are you sure?
No. Are you?
No.
I... I know
he's around here somewhere, okay? I...
Oh, wait, is that...
No. Damn.
Oh, come on,
we've been at this long enough.
We're going back to the car
before our bodies are never found.
Oh, Perez, wait!
Oh, hey.
Where's my mom?
I know she didn't come home last night.
Is she okay?
Yeah.
- No, um...
- Judy.
- I don't know.
Please tell me the truth.
Is... is she in danger?
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know.
She told me Steve was involved
with some dangerous people,
and I found this in his car.
I was too scared to give it to her.
What is this?
I don't know.
There's a bunch of shit in there.
I tried to read what was
on the thumb drive,
but it's all in some weird language,
- like Hebrew or...
- Greek?
Okay.
Thank you for giving this to me.
It was a very responsible thing to do.
I'm super proud of you.
Please, just give me
20 more minutes, okay?
- An hour, tops.
- No.
Just... I can find him, please.
Charlie had nothing to do with this, okay?
What about Judy Hale?
She have something to do with it?
I'm assuming she's the one who told you
we had the picture of Charlie.
Did she blackmail you to say
that you did it alone?
- She write you another check?
- What?
No, no.
Judy's broke, and she would never.
She's a fucking angel on Earth.
I did this. Alone.
Judy is completely innocent.
God, what the hell is it about that woman?
What?
It's like she puts a spell
on every goddamn person she meets.
She told you she ran over your husband,
and yet you somehow still seem to think
that she's some goddamn peach.
Please explain to me how that is possible,
because from where I'm sitting,
none of it makes sense.
Okay, I know how it sounds, all right?
I wanted to hate Judy. I really did.
But it's impossible.
It's like hating a baby or something.
You just can't.
- Why?
- I don't know. It just...
She sees the good in people.
Even when it isn't there.
Hey.
Hey...
Hi. I have some information
on the Steve Wood case.
- You know, the tip line's anonymous.
- Yeah, I heard about that.
But I want you to promise me,
if I give this to you, you're gonna do
everything you can to help Jen.
Help Jen with what?
Help her...
- Wait, did she not come in here?
- No.
- What?
- Why does she need my help?
I meant, like,
just in case she ever finds herself
in a position where she needs help,
I want to help make sure
that you help her.
Okay.
This belongs to Steve.
I happened upon it recently.
You happened upon it?
I don't think he wanted anybody
to find it.
You know,
I heard about those voicemails
that he left you.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
- What did you hear?
- Oh, nothing that surprised me.
Though I'm still trying to figure out
why you'd stay with a guy like that.
Yeah,
I'm trying to figure that out myself.
I guess I thought maybe
you get what you deserve.
Nobody deserves that.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
I listened to that recorder thing
to see if it was anything.
Play it somewhere private.
Where the Chief won't be able
to hear himself.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, my kids are awake.
Am I allowed to get in...
Can I make a phone call?
- Sure.
- Okay, thanks.
Oh, no. Shit.
You'll get better reception
when we're out of the woods.
It doesn't matter.
Like, how am I...
How am I gonna explain this to them?
I mean, I know I have to, but it's like...
They already had such a shitty hand
dealt to them with their dad, and I...
One job...
as their mother, one fucking job,
and I failed.
You said he was threatening you.
You said you asked him to leave.
He has a history of abusive behavior.
That'll carry weight in a courtroom.
Yeah, well...
Steve's family has a lot of connections
around town.
Yeah, I'm aware.
I'm pretty confident that...
...nobody's gonna take pity
on the angry woman who attacked him.
You don't know that.
I do know my kids
are gonna lose their mom.
And I know how it fucking destroyed me
when I lost mine.
When did your mom pass?
Uh...
when I was 19.
From breast cancer.
I lost my mom when I was young, too.
Was she... was she sick?
She was murdered.
Oh, God.
She was trying to protect me
from my stepfather.
She sounds like a good mom.
She was.
I miss her every day.
Me too.
Every day.
- Reception's back.
- Oh, okay.
Um, so what happens now?
Um...
All right.
Well, we'll, uh, go back to the station.
Okay.
You'll give a statement,
with a lawyer present if you choose,
and you will be formally charged.
Okay.
- That's standard procedure.
- Right.
But you're gonna go home.
Huh?
And we are never gonna talk about
what we didn't find out here ever again.
What... what?
We were never here.
Okay, I'm sorry, I don't...
I don't think I understand.
I just...
I don't want to be a cop right now.
I want to be a person.
And sometimes justice just
works itself out.
So go home to your kids.
Tell them you love them.
Because someday
they're gonna miss hearing it.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Judy, is my mom still out for a run?
No.
- Oh, I hope she's okay.
- What is that?
Um...
Can you guys sit down for a minute?
Why?
'Cause I want to talk to you
about something that's really important.
Your mom loves you so, so much.
Oh, shit.
And I love you so, so much.
Yeah, we love you, too.
Thanks.
And...
I just want you to know
that no matter what happens,
you guys are gonna be okay.
Okay?
Okay.
- Your mom is...
- Hi.
- ...coming through the door right now.
- Mom!
Oh, God.
That's not really
the greeting I was expecting.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I am. I am. Are you?
Yeah.
- Hey, Mommy.
- Hi, baby. Oh, God, I love you.
- I love you both so much.
- We know.
Okay.
Listen, I, um...
I just want to explain the letters.
Nope. Nope, you don't.
What letters?
I didn't, uh...
- You didn't?
- No, I didn't.
Good.
What the fuck are you guys talking about?
The...
- surprise.
- The surprise,
'cause your birthday is coming up.
So there's little surprises,
little surprises...
I don't get it.
Trust me, I was there, and I have
no fucking idea what just happened.
- She just let you go?
- Yeah.
- What?
- I mean, I...
I couldn't find him, so...
Well, I carved a heart in the tree
right where he was, so we could find him.
Well, that would have been useful to know
two hours ago.
I didn't know you were going there.
I thought you were going to prison.
Well, that's where I fucking should be.
Well, maybe there's a reason you're not.
Like what, I'm going to cure cancer
or something?
Maybe.
I mean, you'd really have to focus.
I can't believe you're sitting here.
How can you even look at me?
I'm so sorry.
Judy, I'm so sorry that I lied to you
and let you blame yourself.
Fucking horrible thing to do.
It is.
You didn't deserve that.
I didn't.
If I were you, I would get up right now
and walk away
and never fucking talk to me again.
I forgive you.
What?
- I forgive...
- Oh, shut up.
No, you shut up.
I don't want
to carry around any more pain.
I'm tired...
of feeling sad and hurt.
Okay.
And resenting you...
would just be punishing myself.
- So...
- I don't want you to do that.
I don't want you to do that.
How can I not?
I think you have to find a way.
You need to forgive yourself.
- Ew.
- Yeah, I know, it's gross.
But I feel like you've been given
a second chance.
Well, we both have.
Yeah.
I'm sure there's stuff
I have to work on too.
Uh, yeah.
Well, that was a quick response.
I'm open.
You need to start saying "no" more.
I know.
- It's disgusting.
- It is hard.
Oh, God.
I know it's early, but...
can we start drinking?
Do I have to start saying no yet?
You can start tomorrow.
Oh, good, I thought that was a test.
Then yes.
I love you.
I love you too.
So I'm starting to realize that I...
I never really grieved the death
of my mom.
Oh, baby.
Thanks. Um...
I was...
I was 19 when she died, and, um...
At the time, I was...
I was relieved, you know?
She had been sick for most of my life.
I think I was nine
when she was first diagnosed, and um...
She'd be okay...
then the cancer would come back and...
and I would be mad...
at her every time, like it was...
like, something that she was doing,
that she was choosing it.
And then, um...
When her body couldn't fight anymore,
I was mad at her because she couldn't.
And I think I've been mad at myself
for that ever since.
That's rough.
Thanks, Linda.
I'm glad you decided to come back, Jen.
Me too.
Oh, boy.
Thanks, Yolanda.
I wasn't sure if you'd be back.
Don't want to get my hopes up.
That's funny.
Why's that funny?
'Cause that's how I used to feel
when I was a kid, when you'd disappear.
Okay.
We're getting into it.
- We're not.
- Feels like we are.
We're not. I just want
to have a clean slate with you.
I'm not trying to make you feel bad, Mom.
It was just hard not knowing
where you were or what you'd be like
when you came home.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
But it was hard for me, too.
Okay.
You were a tough baby.
You never slept.
You were always crying.
Just really needy.
I was just a kid myself.
I couldn't handle it.
That's why I started using.
A baby can't make you a drug addict.
Of course not. That's not what I'm saying.
Still really sensitive, huh?
Yeah, I still have feelings.
You've always had a good heart.
You know, I was telling Paula,
she's my friend in here,
what a good girl you are.
That you're gonna help me get a lawyer,
get out of here.
You know, I tried to find the money, Mom,
but I couldn't.
Oh. That's too bad.
Sorry.
Don't worry about the money.
You know what would help me even more?
Is if you wrote a letter
to the parole board
telling 'em I've changed,
that I'm better, you know, all that.
They said that would really mean a lot,
coming from you.
Would you do that for me, Judy Anne?
No.
Why not?
You haven't changed.
Daisy! Daisy, where'd you go, girl?
Hey!
Oh!
Hey, did you find something?
You digging for bones?
Daisy, what are you digging for?
- Hi.
- Hello, Miss Hale.
I have something for you.
What?
Thank you. Where did you find them?
They were just sitting
in some police lockers. No big deal.
You don't know what this means to me.
- Really.
- Consider it a thank you.
That bag of Mr. Wood's you "happened upon"
was extremely helpful.
Did you listen to the recordings?
I'm not at liberty to discuss that.
Of course.
But did you hear Hastings' voice?
- Miss Hale.
- Sorry. Is he gonna get in trouble?
Well, suffice it to say, Hastings will
no longer be chief of police.
- Is he going to jail?
- No.
He's going to federal prison.
Along with a few of his Greek friends.
Wow. Wow, wow, wow! Look at us!
Working together to take down the man.
All right, goodbye, Miss Hale.
Hey, Detective? Wait.
I just wanted to say that...
I think you're a really special person.
I sincerely hope I never see you again.
I feel like you don't really mean that.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
♪ You had plenty money, 1922 ♪
♪ You let other women
make a fool of you... ♪
I can reframe it.
♪ Why don't you do right ♪
♪ Like some other men do? ♪
♪ Get out of here
And get me some money, too ♪
Holy fuck!
I told you they were worth something!
Jesus!
What are you gonna do with all of it?
I mean, you can't put in the bank.
I don't want to put it in the bank.
I don't think I understand.
I'm buying you out.
- That's what it's called, right?
- Yeah, that's it.
Uh, this should cover what you gave us
for the down payment on the house,
plus interest.
Are you trying to buy me out of your house
or out of your family, Jennifer?
The house, Lorna, okay?
Just chill out, please.
Look, you are the boys' only grandmother,
and I am...
- Oh, here we go.
- You can do it.
...grateful for that.
Okay, now you're weirding me out.
Look,
I don't want to resent you anymore, Lorna.
It is exhausting.
Which is why I can't keep working for you.
Is that why?
Or is it because you landed
a $20 million listing?
Actually, Lorna,
I want to give you the Wood estate.
As a parting gift.
Are you about to kill yourself?
What's happening?
- No, I'm fine.
- She's fine. You're fine, right?
- I'm fine.
- Yeah.
Just please promise me that you will
take care of Mrs. Wood.
Okay, she...
she needs a friend who understands
what she's going through right now.
Of course.
You two will really get along.
Oh.
For commission on $20 million,
I get along with anyone.
Oh. That's...
Hard to believe
this won't be our home anymore.
I always thought I'd die here.
Oh, I forgot to mention,
your lovely realtor friend
was asking after you.
- She was?
- Mm-hmm.
You should call on her
while you're still in town.
I just hope Stevie will be able
to find us at our next house.
Well...
he could always call, right?
I suppose so.
Why hasn't he?
I don't know, Mom.
Hello?
They did?
Are they sure?
Okay, thank you for letting us know.
Who was that, Benji?
Oh, it's just... just my realtor friend.
Hey, I'm gonna run out
and get some ice cream.
So we have it.
Good idea.
You might want some later.
Judy?
You gotta learn to hide shit better.
Charlie is going to freak out.
You really didn't have to do this.
- I wanted to give him something.
- I know.
I feel like we need a treat.
Yeah, we do!
It's been a year.
- Oh, man, she's been a doozy.
- Oh, my God.
I wanna... I wanna go away.
- Yes!
- Do you want to go away?
- Like, on a vacay?
- Yeah.
I was thinking, like,
a hut-over-the-ocean situation.
Ooh, talk to me like lovers do.
- Ew.
- Come on, you know what I mean.
No, like, Bora Bora, pina coladas.
- Getting caught in the rain?
- Judes.
- Okay, no diggity.
- Nope. Judy.
- Yep, no scrubs.
- Okay.
- No more words.
- Nope.
- More than words?
I like the big butts?
- You like the big butts?
- Can we please stop?
You stop... stop!
What? Oh! Oh, shit!
Oh, my God.
Look what you did.
Look what I did.
- That's your stop sign!
- Yeah.
You made that happen.
You're practically a hero!
- No... No.
- Yes!
I mean, you're probably
gonna save somebody's life.
Oh, come on, let's not get carried away.
It's just a stop sign.
Well, actually,
I will get carried away if I want...
Jen, Jen.
Jen.
Fuck.
Jen. Jen, wake up.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
What happened?
We got hit.
Oh, shit.
♪ You had plenty money, 1922 ♪
♪ You let other women make a fool of you ♪
♪ Why don't you do right ♪
♪ Like some other men do? ♪
♪ Get out of here
And get me some money, too ♪
♪ You're sitting down
Wondering what it's all about ♪
♪ You ain't got no money
They will put you out ♪
♪ Why don't you do right ♪
♪ Like some other men do? ♪
♪ Like some other men do ♪