- Hey.
- Good morning.
Did I snore?
Sometimes I snore like a full animal.
No. You were sleeping like a full angel.
Mm!
You were talking in your sleep.
- Was I?
- Mm-hmm.
What was I saying?
I didn't get all of it,
but you kept saying, "I'm sorry."
- That's weird.
- Yeah.
You sounded kind of sad, actually.
Oh, well, that's strange...
'cause I feel really happy right now.
Okay, I know that you're the chef,
but can I make you breakfast?
I make a mean frittata.
- Really? How mean?
- Hmm.
Hmm. Like, very mean.
Borderline cruel.
Well, I would love
to try your abusive frittata,
but I have to get
to the farmers' market early.
It's chanterelle season, and...
people go batshit.
I don't think you should go.
Sounds dangerous.
I think you should stay here with me.
- I want to.
- I want you to.
You're really hard to leave.
- Good.
- Ooh!
I gotta go. There's, uh...
There's coffee and a grinder
and a French press on the counter,
if you're interested.
I'm very interested.
All right. Get in there.
I love you.
Mm.
Uh, hello.
Oh, hell, no.
Oh, fuck.
Hi! Good morning.
What... This is crazy.
I mean, what are the odds
that we would both know Michelle?
I live here and dated her for six years,
so my odds are pretty good.
Oh, yeah, those are solid odds.
How do you know Michelle?
Uh...
Oh.
- Got it.
- Yeah. She's great.
- Nope.
- Okay.
Do you want some coffee?
- Don't offer me my own espresso.
- Okay. Sorry.
Um, that's a cool shirt.
It's a real statement piece.
- Sweet gams, too.
- Shut up.
Okay.
- Do you need to get that?
- I need you to get out of my house.
Okay. Sorry.
Could you tell Michelle that...
I'll just text her.
What?
Thirty-eight. Speeding.
Forty-two. Illegal!
Sixteen. That's just lame.
This is a lot of work
for a stupid stop sign.
Okay, this is not a lot of work, A.
Pushing your enormous head out
of my vagina was a lot of work.
Gross.
You're telling me.
And B, this is a good thing we're doing.
All right, I think it's important to
contribute positively to your community,
especially when you have made
some... mistakes.
You sound like Judy.
You know what you sound like?
"...Judy."
- Do you want a turn?
- Yeah, okay.
Okay. There you go.
Hey, so...
what's the deal with that guy?
What guy?
That Ben guy.
Um, he's a client.
He's kind of a dork.
Yes, he is.
But he's a nice guy.
Well, you seem chill with him.
'Cause I'm chill.
I'm, like, the most chill.
Hey, slow down, fuck stick!
- What the fuck!
- Yeah, really chill.
Look...
I liked him. Ben.
I kicked his ass at Cruis'n World.
Well, that's 'cause you're so fast.
Exactly.
Prove it.
Give me that thing. Prove it. Go.
Come on. Go, go, go, go!
Oh, come on, Harding!
Put those knees up!
Oh!
Clocking it. Clocking it.
- Huh. Wasn't that bad.
- All right, let me see.
Oh, you think you could go faster?
Honey, come on.
I'm a middle-aged woman wearing heels,
with a bad back. I'm not gonna...
Hold on, I'm not ready, hold on.
- Hey!
- Well, hello.
Is someone doing the strut of shame?
No shame in this game.
Did you have fun last night?
Oh, I had a great night.
Oh, it was...
Anyways. Yeah. It was good.
Good.
Well, you two are very cute together.
- Right?
- Yep.
She's...
awesome.
But, um...
there is one thing.
- Oh, no, what's wrong with her?
- No, no, nothing's wrong with her.
She is... full chef's kiss.
- Okay.
- But, um...
it's just that she has this roommate...
Ew, she has a roommate?
- That's fucking lame.
- It's just...
Wow. Didn't see that coming.
Yeah.
And, um...
it's like a crazy convergence of, like,
a handful of happenstances,
you might say...
Oh, must be Ben.
Why is he here?
I'm showing him more rentals today.
Oh, I thought you looked dressed up.
What? I'm not dressed up.
These are my work clothes.
Yeah, you look like you're gonna work!
You know what?
Eat my fucking butthole, Judy.
I would, but I'm seeing someone now.
Well, fancy meeting you here.
Oh, was I not supposed to...
- No, you were. No, I was just being...
- 'Cause I thought you said...
- You said...
- Never mind. Just come on in.
Just gotta grab the rest of my...
Yeah, sorry. I just...
I may be in shock a little.
Uh, I just got some news.
- News?
- What kind of news?
Um...
...they found Steve's car.
Oh, did they?
Yeah, out in the middle of nowhere.
Completely torched. Barely anything left.
- Oh.
- Oh, that's awful.
- Yeah, that's so awful. Um...
- Oh, my God.
Because it was so torched, I mean,
how did they know that it was Steve's car?
- The VIN number.
- Oh, the VIN number.
- Oh, that is a miracle.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- I guess it was arson,
'cause whoever lit that car on fire
knew what they were doing.
Oh, really?
But I mean, they don't...
they don't know who did it, right?
No, not yet, but they said that
they think that whoever did it was trying
to send a message, like...
like a smoke signal or something?
- Really?
- Well, um...
But do you think that the police
are gonna be able to find,
like, evidence in the car,
you know, like...
like fingerprints or DNA?
I mean, I don't know.
It's too soon to tell.
Let's hope they find something, you know?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Fingers crossed.
At least he wasn't in that car.
My family is clinging to that.
Anyone would, yeah, sure.
Anyway, I don't mean to bail on you,
I just...
- No, it's...
- I gotta...
It's fine.
I'm sure looking for condos is not
the first thing on your mind right now.
Yeah, sorry, my family is just spinning.
- I bet.
- I'm sure.
And somehow I got roped
into organizing a vigil,
whatever that's gonna do.
- Oh, my God!
- That'd be nice
- for the community to get together...
- You shouldn't have to do that...
- ...and keep hope alive.
- Alive.
It's good. Yeah.
I'll be honest with you,
any hope that I do have is kind of on...
life support at the moment.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to get all down about the...
No, it's okay.
- Please. We're...
- Boys can cry.
To us, especially.
- Yeah, I should probably go and...
- Okay, yeah.
...you know, get, uh...
- vigil stuff together, whatever that is.
- Mm-hmm.
I don't even know where to start.
- Oh, it can be really simple.
- Yeah.
Like a...
Get some candles.
- Yeah, and some flowers.
- And some hors d'oeuvres.
Oh, food!
I didn't even think of that. Right.
I should be writing this down.
Uh, can you start over?
Where would I go to get, um...
Candles, what, flowers, food?
You're gonna wanna go
to the gourmet food place on Cedar.
- Okay. Cedar.
- Yeah.
And then if you want flowers,
I mean, I always go to Mission View,
but that's a trek.
You don't go to the...
Cedar's not for flowers,
- so you go to...
- No, you get flowers at a separate place
because the flowers at the supermarket
are gonna die
- in the first five minutes.
- Okay.
You don't need exotic flowers.
You can just get run-of-the-mill roses.
- For flowers?
- Yeah.
And if you want candles,
make sure you get tapers.
- Tapers?
- Yeah.
T-a-p...
You know what?
Why don't you let Judy and I do it?
What?
I mean, really?
Yeah. No, we would be happy to.
- Would we?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm just saying, they found the car, Jen.
I know. I heard him. I was there.
- They're dusting it for DNA.
- I know!
So I just don't think this is maybe
the smartest move we could be making.
It just came out of my mouth, okay?
I couldn't, like, shove it back in there.
I felt bad for him.
Did you see how overwhelmed he was?
I know. I did. I just...
Don't get me wrong,
- I think it's a sweet gesture.
- Thank you.
If you didn't kill the person
that the vigil is for.
Okay, well...
Ben shouldn't have to be doing it.
I mean, I had to plan Ted's funeral
two days after he died,
and it was fucking hell.
And not to sound like
how I'm probably gonna sound right now,
but maybe it's not the worst idea.
I mean, who's gonna suspect that
the people planning the vigil
are the reason that they're having
the vigil in the first place?
- Well, it's a type of logic.
- Okay, well, fine.
More importantly,
it's just a nice thing to do.
I mean, you of all people should get it.
It's like a total WWJD.
A "What would Judy do?"
Thanks.
I'm just trying to be a good person.
Okay.
Well, in that spirit...
I'm gonna say something,
and I would like you
to listen to it like I would.
- Okay.
Michelle's roommate is her ex-girlfriend.
No, fuck that.
- Dude.
- Sorry.
- It's Perez.
- Who's Perez?
- Her ex is Perez.
- Our Perez?
- That Perez.
- Oh, my God.
- I know.
Of all the lesbians in Laguna...
I know, I didn't do it on purpose.
It just happened.
- Pretty organically, actually.
- Well, I'm sorry.
- Why are you sorry?
- Because that's what you would say
when I tell you that
you cannot see her anymore.
- Perez hates you.
- Okay, I think "hate" is a strong word.
Eh, no, that's the word that matches
the feeling that she has for you.
She served you with two restraining orders
in the last six months, Judy.
I can't have you fucking her girlfriend
on the other side of the wall!
- That's not their layout.
- Oh, Judy!
I really like Michelle.
She's the first person since Steve
that I can actually see myself with.
She makes me feel worthy.
I know. I'm sorry.
But you...
you just met her, you know?
And we really just have
to batten down our hatches right now.
I don't want to batten down my hatch.
Judy!
Please.
Hey.
Hi.
Um, could we go somewhere?
Sure.
- Hi.
Oh.
We need to talk.
Yes, we should.
Um...
I'm sorry if my ex was a dick
to you this morning.
Oh, no, it's okay.
No.
No, no, no, it's not okay.
She can't treat you like that.
She's just overprotective.
She was, like,
trying to forbid me from seeing you.
Well, I don't think
I'm her cup of tea, so...
Yeah, I know.
She told me about the thing with the car.
What... what thing... with the... What car?
That you smashed up some car.
Oh.
And then she said that you were a riptide.
Hmm. Yeah.
Look, she doesn't get to decide
who I spend my time with.
I do.
And you do.
I just... I um, can't...
I can't keep spending time with you.
Oh.
Well, that took a turn.
You know, I don't...
I don't have a lot of nights
like the night we just had.
I don't either.
Okay, well, then if this is because
of something she said...
It's not. It's...
Your energy is so...
beautiful...
and honest.
And I...
I just feel karmically like I'm not
in the right place to receive it.
Okay.
Well, I mean, that just sounds
like a woo-woo way of saying,
"It's not you, it's me."
Well, it is me.
Trust me, you don't want anything
to do with me.
I'm sorry, I just can't see you anymore.
I mean, I'll probably see you
walking down the hallway
when you visit your mom, and I'll say hi,
but you know what I mean.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna wash my hands...
before returning to work,
'cause it's state law, so...
Hey.
What do you even wear to a vigil? Huh?
I think I'm going for somewhere in between
court appearance and second wedding.
Sure.
Are you okay?
No.
- Did you talk to Michelle?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm so sorry you had to do that.
I see you're drinking your feelings.
- WWJD.
- Hmm?
"What would Jen do?"
Fair.
Hurtful, but fair.
What is all this?
Oh, uh,
we're helping Ben with his vigil thing.
Did they find his brother?
No. No, not yet.
Well, that sucks.
At least with Dad,
we knew right away, right?
Yeah, well, that's why we're doing it,
you know, just to...
show support, pay it forward.
Yeah, do good stuff,
make up for bad stuff, I got it.
Yep. All that.
I can't do this.
Oh, Jude.
I can't stand there with Steve's friends
and family and pray for his safe return.
I know... I understand, okay?
But don't you think it would be
a little weird if you didn't go?
They won't even notice.
The only time Steve's mom even remotely
cared about me was when I was pregnant.
I can't face her.
You don't have to, all right?
I will protect you. I promise.
All we have to do is show up,
hand out some candles,
and show the community we didn't do it.
Okay? And then we will
get the hell out of there.
Okay.
We will fly right under the radar.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch ♪
♪ Like Steve ♪
♪ He once was lost ♪
♪ But soon he's found... ♪
Hi. Candle?
- Here you go.
- Candle?
Thank you.
- Hi, here's a candle.
Candle?
He has a lot more friends
than I thought he did.
- He's very social.
- Aww.
Here you go.
Take a look around.
What do you see?
Friends, neighbors, family
gathering to share one thing:
hope.
Thank you for coming.
Oh, hi, Len. Candle?
Len. Hi, Len. Like a candle?
Thank you.
- Yeah. I think we did a pretty good job.
- Yeah, are you kidding me?
Shit, I wanna go missing.
- Don't say that.
- Ah, you know what I mean.
- It's her.
- What?
It's his mom.
Okay, just don't... it's okay.
It's okay. Deep breath. Deep breath.
I got you. I got you.
Judy.
- Hello, Eileen.
- Hello, Judy.
You look the same. Bangs.
Yep. You look well.
I'm not.
Oh. I like your scarves.
Benji, find me a chair, would you?
Yes, Mom.
Benji told me
you helped put this together.
She did, because she is the kindest person
that I know.
Hey, will you go do that thing
that we talked about you doing
that I can't do...
- Sorry.
- ...because only you can?
Hi. I'm Jen. I'm, um...
I'm a friend of Ben's.
Would you like a candle?
I can't.
Strong smells trigger my migraines.
Oh, it's electric.
Oh, how novel. Thank you.
It's so kind of everyone to turn up.
I didn't have the strength
to plan this myself.
You understand.
Yeah, I do.
Do you have any children, Jen?
Uh, yeah, I... I have two boys.
Oh, just like me.
Yeah, like you.
Well, I pray you never have to
live through what I'm living through.
Thanks.
It's any mother's worst nightmare.
I'm so sorry.
Judy?
- Oh.
- What a surprise.
Howard! Hi.
Wow, that's a beautiful suit.
Made for me by hand in Mykonos.
How special.
I didn't think we'd see you here.
Oh. Well, I came
to support Steve's family, of course.
Hmm.
Is that why you ratted Steve out?
To support the family?
Oh, there he is.
I found you a comfortable seat, Mom.
Thank you, darling.
Pleasure meeting you, Jen.
Yes.
You hold your boys close.
I'll try.
She likes you.
Oh, hi.
- Hi.
- How are you holding up?
I mean, it's nice to see
so many people come out.
I just wish I...
I don't know. I wish had a better feeling
about the whole thing.
What...
What's your feeling?
He's my twin, Jude...
and if he was out there,
I feel like I would know.
- B-dubs!
- All about the Benjamins.
- What's up? Good to see you.
- Okay.
- Thank you, guys, for coming.
- Hundred percent.
Gotta have faith, man. He's out there.
Right, Judy?
A hundred percent.
Yeah, Steve's gonna turn up
even fucking better than before.
- Find us later for shots!
- Okay.
- Whoo!
- B-dubs!
God, he's always had the worst taste
in friends.
Right?
Better taste in women.
- I don't know about that.
- I do.
Hey, girl.
Sorry, girl.
Thanks, girl.
- Hey, girl.
- I'm just finishing up with a client.
- Oh, okay.
Didn't expect to see you here.
Oh, hi.
Well, Ben's a client, so...
Didn't expect to see you here.
I'm working.
You'd be surprised how often
a perpetrator shows up
to something like this.
Really?
Like moths to a flame.
Hey.
Heidi, right?
Yeah. Sorry, have we met?
Yeah. Once, in Steve's office.
Oh, right,
you're one of his clients, right?
Mm-hmm.
How far along are you?
Oh. Um...
Four months.
Wow.
Yeah.
Is it Steve's?
Um, yeah.
Sorry.
This is just, like, the hardest thing
I've ever been through.
Sorry.
No, no, no. No, don't be sorry.
I'm sorry.
You know what?
You got to keep hope alive, right?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Try to stay positive, okay?
Thank you.
Hey.
You okay?
That girl Steve was seeing...
- Yeah?
- ...is pregnant.
- No.
- Yeah.
Can we please go now?
Yes, I'm so sorry, Judy. I'm so sorry.
Yeah, let's just see if we can get out
of here this way.
Hi, Mom.
Charlie, what are you doing here?
I just thought I should come support Ben.
Oh.
That's actually very sweet,
but we were, um...
- We were just leaving, so...
- We gotta go.
Hi. Thank you all for coming out
for Steve tonight.
- Let's try to sneak out.
- And a very special thank you
to Jen Harding and Judy Hale
for organizing this beautiful,
beautiful vigil.
Thank you, ladies.
- No problem.
- It's no big, no big at all.
So, starting today,
we have set up an anonymous tip line...
with a substantial reward.
Oh, they went with the reward.
I was afraid they wouldn't.
And it's substantial,
so that's good news for us.
- Yeah. It's great.
- So anyone
that has any information,
please come forward...
and help us...
help us bring my...
help us bring my brother home.
- Oh, God.
- Okay.
- I'll get some wine.
- All right.
Thank you.
♪ Pain in my heart ♪
♪ Is treating me cold ♪
♪ Where can my baby be? ♪
♪ Lord, no one knows ♪
♪ Pain in my heart ♪
♪ Just won't let me sleep ♪
♪ Where can my baby be? ♪
Hi, stranger.
Pastor Wayne, hi.
Hey. You all right?
Uh...
I understand.
It's hard living with so much uncertainty.
But God is powerful.
He sees everything.
He sees Steve,
and sooner or later,
He'll bring the truth to light.
You just have to have faith.
I'm sorry, will you excuse me?
♪ Has began to get rough ♪
♪ Said I want you to love me, love me ♪
♪ Love me, baby ♪
♪ Till I get enough ♪
♪ Oh, pain in my heart... ♪
Hey.
- Needed a break?
- Oh.
Yeah.
Me, too.
Thought you didn't drink.
Yeah, I don't.
I...
But I had to do shots for Steve, right?
Right.
I'm so sorry.
Why are you sorry? You don't need
to be sorry. You're, like...
You're, like, the only good part
of this whole thing.
You don't know me that well.
Well, I know you went out of your way
to help me.
That's more than anyone else here's done.
I know you're a good person.
I know you're a good mom.
That's really nice of you to say.
It's true.
If there's a silver lining in all this...
it's meeting you.
Same.
I just...
It's getting a little cold.
I should probably get going.
Oh, no, please,
you don't have to give me...
I insist.
Thank you.
What?
- Long time no see.
- Shit.
Yeah, well, you're not gonna see me
anymore, because I told Michelle that
I'm not gonna hang out with her anymore
because I respect boundaries.
Do you? Because from what I've seen,
you always seem
to be everywhere you shouldn't be.
Well, maybe that's just how you see it.
- It is. That's what I just said.
- Well, yeah, so?
Miss Hale, I've had two major cases
in the last six months,
and there is one person
at the epicenter of them both.
Is it me?
Yes.
I'm warning you, watch yourself,
because I sure as hell am.
Well, you know what? Good.
Go ahead and watch me,
because all you're gonna see
is a good fucking person trying to do
the right fucking thing all the time.
Maybe I shouldn't,
maybe that's where I go wrong,
but I can't help myself because it's
in my stupid fucking nature!
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to go pick up those paper bags
because I don't want a seal to choke!