Hey.
I was looking all over for you.
How long ago did you leave the vigil?
Not long ago enough.
Okay.
Well, that's a nice jacket.
Oh, shit, it's...
It's Ben's. He gave it to me,
and I forgot to give it back to him.
Oh, what else did he give you?
What are you talking about?
Okay, uh, you know what?
I'm really exhausted, and I think
that you are on the dark side of drunk.
I think I'm on the dark side of the truth.
Okay, I don't know what that means.
- Look, let's just...
- Think about it.
I can't. It doesn't make any sense.
So let's just...
Why don't we call it a night?
I need two minutes where I don't feel like
the fucking walls are caving in on me.
- All right, so let's...
- Why did you have Steve Wood's car?
Uh...
'Cause...
So he just gave it to you?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Who just gives someone
an $80,000 Mercedes?
That is a great follow-up question,
and I will answer it.
The answer is...
I was about to close a really big deal
with Steve,
and he pulled out last minute,
so, uh... he felt bad.
Yeah, super bad.
Yeah, so he gave me the car as, like,
an apology for bailing on out.
He's really, really generous.
Then he goes missing...
...and we hadn't switched over the title.
So I put it into storage
until that whole thing plays out,
which could be...
Many, many years.
- And many never even happen.
- No.
Well, how did it get burned?
Well, it wouldn't start,
and then your mom left it
on the side of the road.
Yeah, 'cause I thought it'd be fine.
You know how people love
to burn cars on the side of the road.
Not really.
Yeah, really. People are a fucking mess.
Yeah. Sad.
Well, then shouldn't we go to the police?
Right? At least tell them that Steve
wasn't the one driving the car that night?
That's the right thing to do, right?
- Eh, I mean, I'd...
- Or no?
- Hey, I'd love to do the right thing.
- Me too.
Um, but, kiddo,
we go to the cops,
we're gonna have to tell them
that you were driving the car,
and you would get into a lot of trouble,
and you would never, ever
- get your license, so...
- No.
You're right.
- Oh, fuck.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Aww, baby, baby, no, I know.
I know. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Me, too.
- But it's like, it's okay.
- It is.
We fuck up, you know?
- We all fuck up. Mm-hmm.
- Everybody, a lot of times.
Okay, well...
Yeah.
Just don't take it all on you,
you know what I mean?
- On your shoulders. Night, babe.
- No.
- Sleep tight.
- Good night.
- Oh, my God, I'm gaslighting my own kid.
- Oh!
I'm lying to him.
I'm lying to everyone all the time.
Okay, but you know what?
You don't have to lie to me.
- Okay?
- Hmm?
I saw you kissing Ben, okay?
That was... he kissed me.
It meant nothing.
Okay, but it seems a little unfair to me
since you told me I can't date Michelle
because of the proximity to Perez,
but then you can just
mack out all you want with Ben.
Okay, well, I'm not gonna be
"macking out" with him ever again.
Well, that's too bad,
because in a normal world,
you guys would make a really good couple.
Well, we don't live in a normal world.
Not anymore.
And it's Ben.
It's Steve's fucking brother.
It's Steve's fucking sweet brother. Okay?
Hey, you know what?
Crazier things have happened.
No, literally they have not.
Look, he's coming in the morning
to look at some rentals,
and I'm gonna tell him that
that was a mistake,
and I can't work with him anymore.
If it didn't mean anything,
- why can't you work with him anymore?
- Look, I don't want Ben.
I don't want anyone.
I'm, like, done with all of that.
Well, I'm not.
And what? We're just never supposed
to be happy again?
Just because we...
did some bad things,
we don't deserve love?
You do.
You deserve love.
- So do you.
- No...
Oh, God, I don't know about that.
I do.
Look, if you want to be with Michelle...
I can't stand in your way.
I want you to have whatever you want.
Okay? Just...
stay out of Perez's way.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Don't get all confessy.
I'm gonna be so careful.
- Okay.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Seriously, don't say anything.
- Okay.
- Okay?
'Cause you can get very leaky
out your mouth.
I'm not gonna get leaky.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
You're drunk.
Just a little bit now.
That sobered me up a little.
- You did. You kind of pulled it together.
- Thank you.
Steve Wood tip line.
Ma'am...
Yeah.
Ma'am, I can't hear a word you're saying.
I need you to step away
from the garbage disposal, please.
Yeah... Yeah, it's the garbage...
- My man.
- Oh. Chief Hastings. Hi.
How's it going?
Any solid leads?
Uh, define "solid."
I mean, having a guy go missing
with an identical twin walking around
present its own, uh... challenges.
Well, if you're not up for the challenge,
I could put someone else on this, Prager.
I didn't say that. Uh...
I'm just saying,
this reward thing, it's tricky.
$100,000, it makes people see
what they wanna see.
Well, what I wanna see is some justice
for Steve Wood.
- He's a good guy from a good family.
- Hmm.
Then why is the FBI investigating him
for money laundering?
A better question is,
why did his ex-fiancée turn him in
and then drain his bank account?
Oh, that's another question,
not sure if it's better.
It's better.
Judy Hale is a bitter,
conniving grifter out for money,
and my hunch says revenge.
Really?
You think an arts-and-crafts teacher
for old folks is a better suspect
than the Greek Mafia he's working for?
The Greek Mafia.
Uh-huh.
Prager...
you're not starting to lose it again,
are you?
Tsk.
Hmm.
Answer the phone, bro.
I'm starting to worry about you.
I'm not your bro, homie.
Steve Wood tip line.
You saw him on horseback. Huh.
What kind of horse?
- Hi.
Hi.
I tried to call, but then I was like,
this is an in-person thing.
Have you been drinking?
Sure.
Did I wake you?
You did.
Oh.
I just want to tell you
that I can't stop thinking about you.
Hmm.
And that I'm sorry that I acted stupid
and weird yesterday,
and that I just shouldn't have
pushed you away.
Judy, this is, uh...
Look, I think you need to maybe
take a beat,
sober on up,
and, uh, just think about
what you really want.
No, I know what I really want.
Do you?
I like you, Michelle.
Like, I like you like you.
Like, I wanted to come with a boom box
over my head like in Say Anything,
but I know that that's played out, so...
Yeah, it's totally played out,
but I would have liked it.
Shit! I can come back.
No, I get the sentiment.
I just think you are so smart
and funny and beautiful and sexy and...
your food is amazing...
and your eyes are delicious,
and I just really want to kiss you
right now if you'll let me.
Is your roommate home?
- She's on the night shift.
- Oh, great.
- Hi.
Um, these are for you.
Oh, thank you. Um...
- You really didn't have to...
- Oh, they're from my mom...
um, to say thank you for the vigil.
She's very grateful, and me, too. I'm...
very grateful, and so is she.
Well, it's the least I could do.
Oh, before I forget, your jacket.
- Um, here you go.
- Thanks.
Um...
I guess we should probably talk
about what happened last night.
Oh, no. What, um...
What... what did I do?
Did I say something stupid?
Oh, you don't remember?
I... I was really drunk.
It was kind of a blackout situation.
Uh...
Oh, no. Tell me I didn't do anything dumb.
No, no, you didn't.
It's just,
I saw that you were drinking and...
Yeah, yeah, um...
I mean, no judgment.
I just... was just concerned.
Thanks.
A week ago, I was a year sober.
Mm-hmm.
Woke up this morning,
and I had one of those mirror moments
where you just kind of want
to erase everything you see.
Don't relate to that at all.
Um, listen, actually,
I don't think
I can really help you anymore.
Just the rental market is dead, and...
How's the buyer's market?
Why?
Are you moving here permanently?
No, um, but...
it's looking like my parents have to sell,
because of Steve.
- Oh.
- It's a long story. I can't get into it,
- or I'll immediately start drinking again.
- Don't do that.
Um, but my mother was so taken with you,
that she wants you to be her realtor.
Oh, well, that's so nice.
But, um, yeah, I can't take that on.
Yeah, well, she wants someone
that she can trust,
and, you know, who she knows
is gonna look out for them.
Yeah, I know, it's just,
in my life right now...
I mean, the house has gotta be worth
at least 10 to 15 mil.
- Sorry to say "mil." That's icky.
- Yeah.
But if anyone should get that commission,
I mean, it's you.
I mean, I could take a look at it.
Hi, Hazel.
Flo?
Then in the early '80s,
we ripped up most of the marble floors
because it was slippery.
- Oh, so slippery. Yeah.
- Mm-hmm. Flashy.
Of course.
I didn't need my home to be a showcase.
I wanted it to be a safe space
for my children.
- Mm-hmm.
- It was, Mom.
No, it's a great place for kids.
Oh, thank you.
And thank you again
for what you did for us yesterday
with that beautiful vigil.
Oh, it was nothing.
It was everything.
You gave us hope,
just when things seemed the darkest.
When Steven gets home,
I'm going to make sure
he thanks you properly.
That's uh... Thank you.
- Benji, I'll let you finish the tour.
- Okay.
I need to rest my knees. I'm...
bone on bone. Hmm.
- Careful on the stairs, Mom.
- Mm-hmm. I'll take them one at a time.
- She'll take them one at a time.
- Hmm.
- Are you okay?
- Hmm?
Yeah, no, no, it's just...
Just a lot to take in.
Yeah. Subtle, right?
- Yeah.
- And the tour's just getting started.
Oh.
You know, you don't need to...
I can show myself around.
Oh, actually you can't.
People do get lost here.
I don't want to end up finding
your dusty skeleton in the maid's chamber
ten years from now.
I'm gonna pretend
you did not say "maid's chamber."
Me, too.
Uh, this is the sitting room,
where you can see my mother's love
of tassels on full display.
Oh, um, don't look at that.
Uh, that's not part of the tour.
Oh.
Yeah, that's eight-year-old me
wearing a turtleneck at the beach.
Hmm. What, were you cold?
No, quite the opposite.
It was a very hot summer.
No, it was because of the surgeries.
I had scars, and Steve didn't.
And I wanted all the girls to like me,
so I...
I thought, why advertise all that?
You know?
But they didn't like me anyway, so...
Come on, yeah, they did.
No. Believe it or not, hospital boy
whose best friend was a nurse
wasn't exactly bringing
all the girls to the yard.
Oh, fuck those girls.
They don't deserve you.
'Cause I...
I think that scars show that
you went through something hard,
and you survived.
And it's your story.
I like that.
Just how I look at it.
Yeah.
Is that an elephant made out of ivory?
- And we're walking.
- 'Cause that's fucked up.
Interesting.
Hi, I'm looking for a Flo Gutierrez.
I mean, I think her first name
is actually Flora.
Are you family?
- No, but I'm...
- ICU is family only. Sorry.
Right. Thanks.
Hey, Michelle.
- Judy. What are you doing here?
- Hey.
Hey. I came as soon as I heard.
Is she okay?
I don't know. She, um...
She had a stroke,
and they're, uh, doing some tests.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
Can I do anything?
No. Thank you. You don't...
You didn't even have to come.
Well, I know that, but...
Jesus Christ, it won't go away.
You're not allowed to be back here.
Ana, could you stop being a cop
for two seconds, please?
No.
Have you not heard a word I've said
about her?
Yes, I did.
She's a riptide,
whatever the fuck that means.
It's a metaphor,
but allow me to spell it out for you.
At best, she's an unstable accused stalker
who I have personally arrested
for destruction of property.
It wasn't a stalk, more of a follow,
and the property was that car...
At worst,
she's involved in an active investigation
where her ex-fiancé is currently missing
and possibly dead.
- What?
- Yeah.
So forgive me for being protective,
because I don't want you
to end up like him.
Is that true?
I, um...
I mean...
Technically, he is missing.
But I, um...
You know what, I...
I can't deal with this right now.
There's...
This is too much.
I'm so sorry.
- I just want to be with my mom.
- Okay.
Alone.
- Oh... Michelle.
- Don't.
I'll just... go this way.
Listen, I know that you have been
making an effort to do the right thing
and to be a better person,
and I just want you to know that
I see you.
Okay.
I see you too.
No, like, the inner you.
Anyway, my work has been picking up,
and what I'm saying
is that if you keep
on the right path here,
there may be a car in your future.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm. Yep.
Good behavior pays off, bud.
- What the fuck?
- Hmm?
All right, go inside.
See if we have any paint.
Karen!
- Jeff.
- Jen.
- Uh, yeah, I'm looking for Karen.
- I'm doing great.
- How are you?
- Okay.
Wait, is that not what you just asked?
No, not at all. Anyway, I was wondering...
We're getting divorced, Karen and I,
so it's, like...
- Oh, wow. I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
Well, with the few details that I know,
it kind of makes sense.
- Anyway, I was wondering...
- Thank you, I appreciate it.
But, you know, like,
it's for the best, right?
No doubt.
Obviously I feel terrible
about lying to Karen.
- She did not deserve that.
- Mnh-mnh. Mnh-mnh.
It's not a lie to say
that I have had love for her.
It's just different with Sebastian.
It seems like it would be.
Love came knocking on my door,
and I had to answer.
I mean, that happens, what, once,
maybe twice in a lifetime, right?
- Yeah.
- In any case, thank you
for not telling Karen
before I got a chance to.
- I owe you one.
- Oh, I have the one.
- Um, we were just vandalized.
- Oh.
And I was wondering if I could look
at your street camera footage
from the last hour just
to see if it caught anything.
- Sure.
- Please.
It's...
Don't look at that.
Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, I don't make a habit of it.
- No?
- The last hour. Here you go.
People have, on the bright side,
been relatively supportive.
Not Karen, obviously.
I think this is something that's gonna
stick with her for a while.
I think she's gonna remember it,
but at least to my face, my parents...
I need another favor.
- Sure.
- Could you please delete
- that from the cloud?
- Sure.
And basically anything
from the last month or so?
Why? Are you also fucking Sebastian?
Seriously, I need you to delete it.
- Will do.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- I'm gonna be okay.
- Great.
It is great.
Oh!
Hi.
Your baby's beautiful.
Oh, thanks, she's not mine.
I'm just a cuddler.
You're a what?
A cuddler.
We volunteer to hold the babies
when the parents aren't around.
Oh, I didn't even know that was a thing.
Yeah.
I feel like I get more out of it
than the babies do.
You hold them for two seconds,
and you forget there's anything bad
in the world.
Yeah, I bet.
Wow, what a dream job.
You should do it.
Wait. Seriously?
- How do you even...
- Oh, it's easy.
You just sit for an interview...
- Okay.
- ...get a little training,
and then you're in.
Okay.
After they do a background check.
Just gotta weed out any criminals.
Yeah.
So, maybe I'll see you around.
Yeah, maybe.
Hi.
Oh, hey.
You want to explain to me
why Parker felt the need
to write "I know what you did"
on our fucking garage door?
- Huh?
- Oh, shit.
- What did you do?
- Nothing!
- Charlie.
- I...
I just...
started hanging out with somebody else.
- You cheated on her?
- No...
Parker and I were never serious.
We were just hanging out.
You know what? She thought it was
serious enough to vandalize our house.
- It's not my fault she's crazy.
- Okay...
She's not crazy.
You treated her like shit,
so she was driven crazy.
- Okay...
- I mean, come on.
Just imagine how you would feel
if you loved someone and you found out
that they were fucking around on you.
You know what?
You would feel worthless.
And you would always wonder
why you weren't good enough.
So don't be that guy, Charlie.
I'm not. I'm not.
I just realized
I don't really like Parker.
Hmm.
And Natalie's different. She's chill.
Okay, she's chill? I don't...
Well, she doesn't care about
Instagram followers, or...
Okay.
Look...
And she lost her dad, too.
So...
we have stuff in common, I guess.
All right. Just...
Just be good to her.
Okay? Be kind.
Apologize to Parker.
Please.
You need to clean up your messes.
Starting with the garage door.
- Yeah?
- That was a demand, not a suggestion.
- Oh, right. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Is Flo all right?
Look, I'm leaving.
I just want to know if she's okay.
She's on life support.
Doesn't look good.
Are you okay?
No.
But I will be.
Michelle is really lucky to have you.
They're my family.
Flo's the closest thing to a mother
I've had in a really long time.
I understand.
I lost my mom a while ago.
Can I give you a hug?
- No.
- Okay.
♪ My love must be a kind of blind love ♪
♪ I can't see anyone but you ♪
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ Are the stars out tonight? ♪
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ I don't know if it's cloudy or bright ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
♪ I only have eyes ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Dear ♪
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ The moon may be high ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ But I can't see a thing in the sky ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
♪ I only have eyes... ♪
Steve Wood tip line.
Hi.
Um, I feel like I have something
you might want to see.
Steve?
Who is this?
Hello. Um...
Hi, can I please speak with Eleanor Hale?
This is her daughter.
She did?
When?
No, no. I understand.
Sure. Thank you.
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ The moon may be high ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ But I can't see a thing in the sky ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
♪ I only have eyes... ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- ♪ You are here, and so am I ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
- Hi.
Um, I don't wanna lie to you.
And I don't you think that
I kissed you because I was drunk.
The truth is...
I've wanted to kiss you for a long time,
like...
like, the whole time.
So you do remember.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's pretty much
all I remember about anything.
- ♪ For you ♪
- ♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
♪ Sha-bop, sha-bop ♪
Mm!